arthisoft.com 2014-06-23

# Privacy Policy - Arth I-Soft

Arth I-Soft may collect information of customers who are interested in buying its products or services. The information provided by customers is based on their own decision and consent. You are aware and understand that there is no obligation on you to provide your personal information. You agree and understand that Arth I-Soft is under no obligation to verify the accuracy of information source whomever it concerns. You also agree to provide correct information to avoid fraudulent activity.

Arth I-Soft takes security measures to protect information both online and off-line. Customer information that is stored with Arth I-Soft has restricted access to employees who need that information to perform their specific job. Arth I-Soft may log IP addresses for better web administration and maintaining the integrity of our services.

Arth I-Soft may share aggregated demographic and other information with our partners and affiliates. Information provided to Arth I-Soft will not be sold or rented to any unrelated third parties without the express consent of the information provider, except that Arth I-Soft may disclose data to its affiliates and business partners who have established similar privacy standards.

Arth I-Soft website may have links to external websites and are out of scope of this privacy statement. Arth I-Soft is not responsible for the accuracy of information provided by external websites and has no control over the privacy practices observed by those websites.

Arth I-Soft reserves the right to change/amend this privacy statement at any time. Customers of Arth I-Soft must have to check privacy statement on the website periodically to remain aware of any amendments that may be made from time to time. Use of website or Arth I-Soft product or service constitutes your acceptance of those changes.
